import { Question } from "@/types/Question";

export const questionsByWeek: { [week: string]: Question[] } = {
	week1: [
		{
			question: '"Amigo" or "Amiga" means',
			options: ["Enemy", "Friend", "Stranger", "Relative"],
			answer: "Friend"
		},
		{
			question: '"Bolsa" translates to',
			options: ["Shoe", "Bag", "Book", "Water"],
			answer: "Bag"
		},
		{
			question: '"Cebolla" is the Spanish word for',
			options: ["Carrot", "Onion", "Potato", "Tomato"],
			answer: "Onion"
		},
		{
			question: '"Casa" means',
			options: ["Car", "Cat", "House", "Church"],
			answer: "House"
		},
		{
			question: '"Chaqueta" is a',
			options: ["Shoe", "Hat", "Jacket", "Glove"],
			answer: "Jacket"
		},
		{
			question: '"Delfín" translates to',
			options: ["Dog", "Dolphin", "Deer", "Duck"],
			answer: "Dolphin"
		},
		{
			question: '"Espejo" means',
			options: ["Window", "Door", "Mirror", "Wall"],
			answer: "Mirror"
		},
		{
			question: '"Fuente" can mean',
			options: ["River", "Fountain", "Spring", "Source"],
			answer: "Fountain"
		},
		{
			question: '"Gerente" is a',
			options: ["Teacher", "Manager", "Doctor", "Lawyer"],
			answer: "Manager"
		},
		{
			question: '"Gato" translates to',
			options: ["Dog", "Horse", "Cat", "Bird"],
			answer: "Cat"
		},
		{
			question: '"Huevo" means',
			options: ["Milk", "Bread", "Cheese", "Egg"],
			answer: "Egg"
		},
		{
			question: '"Iglesia" is a',
			options: ["School", "Hospital", "Church", "Library"],
			answer: "Church"
		},
		{
			question: '"Jirafa" translates to',
			options: ["Giraffe", "Zebra", "Elephant", "Lion"],
			answer: "Giraffe"
		},
		{
			question: '"Kiosko" means',
			options: ["Store", "Kiosk", "Market", "Mall"],
			answer: "Kiosk"
		},
		{
			question: '"Libro" is a',
			options: ["Pen", "Book", "Pencil", "Notebook"],
			answer: "Book"
		},
		{
			question: '"Llave" means',
			options: ["Lock", "Door", "Key", "Window"],
			answer: "Key"
		},
		{
			question: '"Manzana" translates to',
			options: ["Banana", "Orange", "Apple", "Grape"],
			answer: "Apple"
		},
		{
			question: '"Naranja" means',
			options: ["Apple", "Banana", "Orange", "Grape"],
			answer: "Orange"
		},
		{
			question: '"Ñame" is a',
			options: ["Fruit", "Vegetable", "Meat", "Fish"],
			answer: "Yam"
		},
		{
			question: '"Oveja" translates to',
			options: ["Goat", "Cow", "Sheep", "Horse"],
			answer: "Sheep"
		},
		{
			question: '"Pelo" means',
			options: ["Skin", "Hair", "Nail", "Eye"],
			answer: "Hair"
		},
		{
			question: '"Queso" is',
			options: ["Bread", "Meat", "Cheese", "Milk"],
			answer: "Cheese"
		},
		{
			question: '"Rana" translates to',
			options: ["Fish", "Lizard", "Frog", "Snake"],
			answer: "Frog"
		},
		{
			question: '"Sol" means',
			options: ["Moon", "Star", "Sun", "Sky"],
			answer: "Sun"
		},
		{
			question: '"Tortuga" is a',
			options: ["Snake", "Lizard", "Turtle", "Crocodile"],
			answer: "Tortoise"
		},
		{
			question: '"Uvas" means',
			options: ["Bananas", "Apples", "Oranges", "Grapes"],
			answer: "Grapes"
		},
		{
			question: '"Vaca" translates to',
			options: ["Horse", "Sheep", "Cow", "Pig"],
			answer: "Cow"
		},
		{
			question: '"Wafle" is a',
			options: ["Bread", "Pancake", "Waffle", "Cake"],
			answer: "Waffle"
		},
		{
			question: '"Xilófono" means',
			options: ["Guitar", "Drum", "Xylophone", "Piano"],
			answer: "Xylophone"
		},
		{
			question: '"Yema" can mean',
			options: ["Skin", "Seed", "Yolk", "Nucleus"],
			answer: "Yolk"
		},
		{
			question: '"Zapatos" translates to',
			options: ["Socks", "Gloves", "Hats", "Footwears"],
			answer: "Footwears"
		}
	],
	week2: [
		{
			question: '"Uno" means',
			options: ["Zero", "One", "Two", "Ten"],
			answer: "One"
		},
		{
			question: '"Dos" translates to',
			options: ["One", "Three", "Two", "Four"],
			answer: "Two"
		},
		{
			question: '"Tres" means',
			options: ["Two", "Four", "Three", "Five"],
			answer: "Three"
		},
		{
			question: '"Cuatro" translates to',
			options: ["Three", "Five", "Four", "Six"],
			answer: "Four"
		},
		{
			question: '"Cinco" means',
			options: ["Four", "Six", "Five", "Seven"],
			answer: "Five"
		},
		{
			question: '"Seis" translates to',
			options: ["Five", "Seven", "Six", "Eight"],
			answer: "Six"
		},
		{
			question: '"Siete" means',
			options: ["Six", "Eight", "Seven", "Nine"],
			answer: "Seven"
		},
		{
			question: '"Ocho" translates to',
			options: ["Seven", "Nine", "Eight", "Ten"],
			answer: "Eight"
		},
		{
			question: '"Nueve" means',
			options: ["Eight", "Ten", "Nine", "Eleven"],
			answer: "Nine"
		},
		{
			question: '"Diez" translates to',
			options: ["Nine", "Eleven", "Ten", "Twelve"],
			answer: "Ten"
		},
		{
			question: '"Once" means',
			options: ["Ten", "Twelve", "Eleven", "Thirteen"],
			answer: "Eleven"
		},
		{
			question: '"Doce" translates to',
			options: ["Eleven", "Thirteen", "Twelve", "Fourteen"],
			answer: "Twelve"
		},
		{
			question: '"Trece" means',
			options: ["Twelve", "Fourteen", "Thirteen", "Fifteen"],
			answer: "Thirteen"
		},
		{
			question: '"Catorce" translates to',
			options: ["Thirteen", "Fifteen", "Fourteen", "Sixteen"],
			answer: "Fourteen"
		},
		{
			question: '"Quince" means',
			options: ["Fourteen", "Sixteen", "Fifteen", "Seventeen"],
			answer: "Fifteen"
		},
		{
			question: '"Dieciséis" translates to',
			options: ["Fifteen", "Seventeen", "Sixteen", "Eighteen"],
			answer: "Sixteen"
		},
		{
			question: '"Diecisiete" means',
			options: ["Sixteen", "Eighteen", "Seventeen", "Nineteen"],
			answer: "Seventeen"
		},
		{
			question: '"Dieciocho" translates to',
			options: ["Seventeen", "Nineteen", "Eighteen", "Twenty"],
			answer: "Eighteen"
		},
		{
			question: '"Diecinueve" means',
			options: ["Eighteen", "Twenty", "Nineteen", "Twenty-one"],
			answer: "Nineteen"
		},
		{
			question: '"Veinte" translates to',
			options: ["Nineteen", "Twenty-one", "Twenty", "Twenty-two"],
			answer: "Twenty"
		},
		{
			question: '"Treinta" means',
			options: ["Twenty", "Forty", "Thirty", "Fifty"],
			answer: "Thirty"
		},
		{
			question: '"Cuarenta" translates to',
			options: ["Thirty", "Fifty", "Forty", "Sixty"],
			answer: "Forty"
		},
		{
			question: '"Cincuenta" means',
			options: ["Forty", "Sixty", "Fifty", "Seventy"],
			answer: "Fifty"
		},
		{
			question: '"Sesenta" translates to',
			options: ["Fifty", "Seventy", "Sixty", "Eighty"],
			answer: "Sixty"
		},
		{
			question: '"Setenta" means',
			options: ["Sixty", "Eighty", "Seventy", "Ninety"],
			answer: "Seventy"
		},
		{
			question: '"Ochenta" translates to',
			options: ["Seventy", "Ninety", "Eighty", "Hundred"],
			answer: "Eighty"
		},
		{
			question: '"Noventa" means',
			options: ["Eighty", "Hundred", "Ninety", "Zero"],
			answer: "Ninety"
		},
		{
			question: '"Cien" translates to',
			options: ["Ninety", "Zero", "Hundred", "Thousand"],
			answer: "Hundred"
		},
		{
			question: 'The Spanish number for "Thirty-four" is',
			options: ["Treinta", "Treinta y tres", "Treinta y cuatro", "Treinta y cinco"],
			answer: "Treinta y cuatro"
		},
		{
			question: 'The Spanish number for "Thirty-five" is',
			options: ["Treinta y cuatro", "Treinta y cinco", "Treinta y seis", "Treinta y siete"],
			answer: "Treinta y cinco"
		},
		{
			question: 'The Spanish number for "Thirty-six" is',
			options: ["Treinta y cinco", "Treinta y seis", "Treinta y siete", "Treinta y ocho"],
			answer: "Treinta y seis"
		},
		{
			question: 'The Spanish number for "Thirty-seven" is',
			options: ["Treinta y seis", "Treinta y siete", "Treinta y ocho", "Treinta y nueve"],
			answer: "Treinta y siete"
		},
		{
			question: 'The Spanish number for "Thirty-eight" is',
			options: ["Treinta y siete", "Treinta y ocho", "Treinta y nueve", "Cuarenta"],
			answer: "Treinta y ocho"
		},
		{
			question: 'The Spanish number for "Thirty-nine" is',
			options: ["Treinta y ocho", "Treinta y nueve", "Cuarenta", "Cincuenta"],
			answer: "Treinta y nueve"
		},
		{
			question: 'Additional Spanish unique number: "Mil" translates to',
			options: ["Hundred", "Thousand", "Million", "Billion"],
			answer: "Thousand"
		},
		{
			question: 'Additional Spanish unique number: "Un millón" means',
			options: ["Thousand", "Million", "Billion", "Trillion"],
			answer: "Million"
		}
	],
	week3: [
		{
			question: '"El libro" translates to',
			options: ["Pen", "Book", "Pencil", "Notebook"],
			answer: "Book"
		},
		{
			question: '"El bolígrafo" means',
			options: ["Pencil", "Pen", "Marker", "Eraser"],
			answer: "Pen"
		},
		{
			question: '"El sacapunta" translates to',
			options: ["Pencil", "Notebook", "Sharpener", "Glue"],
			answer: "Sharpener"
		},
		{
			question: '"El escritorio" means',
			options: ["Chair", "Table", "Desk", "Computer"],
			answer: "Desk"
		},
		{
			question: '"El cuaderno" translates to',
			options: ["Book", "Notebook", "Paper", "Diary"],
			answer: "Notebook"
		},
		{
			question: '"El mapa" means',
			options: ["Chart", "Graph", "Map", "Poster"],
			answer: "Map"
		},
		{
			question: '"El techo" translates to',
			options: ["Wall", "Ground", "Floor", "Ceiling"],
			answer: "Ceiling"
		},
		{
			question: '"El ordenador" means',
			options: ["Laptop", "Computer", "Tablet", "Phone"],
			answer: "Computer"
		},
		{
			question: '"El lápiz" translates to',
			options: ["Pen", "Marker", "Pencil", "Crayon"],
			answer: "Pencil"
		},
		{
			question: '"La papelera" means',
			options: ["Paper", "Notebook", "Dust bin", "Trash can"],
			answer: "Dust bin"
		},
		{
			question: '"La puerta" translates to',
			options: ["Window", "Wall", "Entrance", "Door"],
			answer: "Door"
		},
		{
			question: '"La mesa" means',
			options: ["Chair", "Desk", "Table", "Shelf"],
			answer: "Table"
		},
		{
			question: '"La silla" translates to',
			options: ["Table", "Desk", "Bench", "Chair"],
			answer: "Chair"
		},
		{
			question: '"La luz" means',
			options: ["Sun", "Lamp", "Light", "Candle"],
			answer: "Light"
		},
		{
			question: '"Los auriculares" translates to',
			options: ["Earrings", "Headphones", "Headset", "Microphone"],
			answer: "Headset"
		},
		{
			question: '"Los datos personales" means',
			options: ["Family history", "Personal information", "Personal details", "Personal records"],
			answer: "Personal details"
		},
		{
			question: '"El nombre" translates to',
			options: ["Surname", "Address", "Name", "Title"],
			answer: "Name"
		},
		{
			question: '"La edad" means',
			options: ["Height", "Weight", "Age", "Year"],
			answer: "Age"
		},
		{
			question: '"La nacionalidad" translates to',
			options: ["Country", "Region", "State", "Nationality"],
			answer: "Nationality"
		},
		{
			question: '"El país" means',
			options: ["City", "Province", "State", "Country"],
			answer: "The country"
		}
	],
	week4: [
		{
			question: 'The nationality of Argentina is',
			options: ["argentino", "boliviano", "chileno", "colombiano"],
			answer: "argentino"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for Bolivia is',
			options: ["argentino", "boliviano", "chileno", "colombiano"],
			answer: "boliviano"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for Chile is',
			options: ["argentino", "boliviano", "chileno", "colombiano"],
			answer: "chileno"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for Colombia is',
			options: ["argentino", "boliviano", "chileno", "colombiano"],
			answer: "colombiano"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for Costa Rica is',
			options: ["costarricense", "cubano", "ecuatoriano", "salvadoreño"],
			answer: "costarricense"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for Cuba is',
			options: ["costarricense", "cubano", "ecuatoriano", "salvadoreño"],
			answer: "cubano"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for Ecuador is',
			options: ["costarricense", "cubano", "ecuatoriano", "salvadoreño"],
			answer: "ecuatoriano"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for El Salvador is',
			options: ["costarricense", "cubano", "ecuatoriano", "salvadoreño"],
			answer: "salvadoreño"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for Guatemala is',
			options: ["guatemalteco", "hondureño", "nicaragüense", "panameño"],
			answer: "guatemalteco"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for Mexico is',
			options: ["mejicano", "nicaragüense", "panameño", "paraguayo"],
			answer: "mejicano"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for Germany is',
			options: ["alemán", "austriaco", "francés", "italiano"],
			answer: "alemán"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for Austria is',
			options: ["alemán", "austriaco", "francés", "italiano"],
			answer: "austriaco"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for France is',
			options: ["alemán", "austriaco", "francés", "italiano"],
			answer: "francés"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for Canada is',
			options: ["canadiense", "estadounidense", "británico", "australiano"],
			answer: "canadiense"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for United States is',
			options: ["canadiense", "estadounidense", "británico", "australiano"],
			answer: "estadounidense"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for Great Britain is',
			options: ["canadiense", "estadounidense", "británico", "australiano"],
			answer: "británico"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for China is',
			options: ["chino", "japonés", "coreano", "vietnamita"],
			answer: "chino"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for Japan is',
			options: ["chino", "japonés", "coreano", "vietnamita"],
			answer: "japonés"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for Poland is',
			options: ["polaco", "italiano", "francés", "alemán"],
			answer: "polaco"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for Russia is',
			options: ["ruso", "ucraniano", "bielorruso", "polaco"],
			answer: "ruso"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for Denmark is',
			options: ["danés", "noruego", "sueco", "finlandés"],
			answer: "danés"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for Saudi Arabia is',
			options: ["saudí", "árabe", "emiratí", "kuwaití"],
			answer: "saudí"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for Bulgaria is',
			options: ["búlgaro", "rumano", "serbio", "griego"],
			answer: "búlgaro"
		},
		{
			question: 'The nationality for Greece is',
			options: ["búlgaro", "rumano", "griego", "albanés"],
			answer: "griego"
		}
	],
	week5: [
		{
			question: '"¡Hola!" means',
			options: ["Goodbye", "Hello", "Sorry", "Thanks"],
			answer: "Hello"
		},
		{
			question: '"Discúlpeme" translates to',
			options: ["Hello", "Thank you", "Excuse me", "Goodbye"],
			answer: "Excuse me"
		},
		{
			question: '"Perdón" means',
			options: ["Sorry", "Pardon", "Forgive me", "Excuse me"],
			answer: "Pardon"
		},
		{
			question: '"Señorito/ta" translates to',
			options: ["Mister", "Master", "Miss", "Madam"],
			answer: "Master/Miss"
		},
		{
			question: '"Señor/ra" means',
			options: ["Sir", "Mister", "Missus", "Madam"],
			answer: "Mister/Missus | Sir/Madam"
		},
		{
			question: '"Buenos días" means',
			options: ["Good night", "Good afternoon", "Good morning", "Good evening"],
			answer: "Good morning"
		},
		{
			question: '"Buenas tardes" translates to',
			options: ["Good morning", "Good night", "Good afternoon", "Good evening"],
			answer: "Good afternoon"
		},
		{
			question: '"Buenas noches" means',
			options: ["Good morning", "Good afternoon", "Good evening", "Good night"],
			answer: "Good night"
		},
		{
			question: '"Bienvenido/da" translates to',
			options: ["Hello", "Goodbye", "Welcome", "Nice to meet you"],
			answer: "Welcome"
		},
		{
			question: '"¿Qué tal?" is an informal way of saying',
			options: ["How are you?", "What's your name?", "What's up?", "Nice to meet you"],
			answer: "What's up? (informal)"
		},
		{
			question: '"¿Qué pasa?" means',
			options: ["What's up? (informal)", "What's up? (formal)", "How are you?", "What do you do?"],
			answer: "What's up? (formal)"
		},
		{
			question: '"Nada, todo bien" translates to',
			options: ["Nothing, all bad", "Everything is fine", "Nothing, all good", "Everything is wrong"],
			answer: "Nothing, all good"
		},
		{
			question: '"¿Cómo estás?" means',
			options: ["How are you? (formal)", "What's your name?", "How are you? (informal)", "What do you do?"],
			answer: "How are you? (informal)"
		},
		{
			question: '"¿Cómo está?" translates to',
			options: ["How are you? (informal)", "What's your name?", "How are you? (formal)", "What do you do?"],
			answer: "How are you? (formal)"
		},
		{
			question: '"Estoy bien" means',
			options: ["I am bad", "I am okay", "I am fine", "I am tired"],
			answer: "I am fine; I am good"
		},
		{
			question: '"¿A qué te dedicas?" means',
			options: ["What are you doing?", "What do you do? (formal)", "What do you do? (informal)", "What is your job?"],
			answer: "What you do? (informal)"
		},
		{
			question: '"¿A qué se dedica?" translates to',
			options: ["What are you doing?", "What do you do? (informal)", "What do you do? (formal)", "What is your job?"],
			answer: "What you do? (formal)"
		},
		{
			question: '"Soy" means',
			options: ["You are", "They are", "I am", "We are"],
			answer: "I am"
		},
		{
			question: '"¿Cómo te llamas?" means',
			options: ["What is your name? (formal)", "What do you do?", "How are you?", "What is your name? (informal)"],
			answer: "What is your name? (informal)"
		},
		{
			question: '"¿Cómo se llama?" translates to',
			options: ["What is your name? (informal)", "What do you do?", "How are you?", "What is your name? (formal)"],
			answer: "What is your name? (formal)"
		},
		{
			question: '"Me llamo" means',
			options: ["My name", "I am", "I call", "I speak"],
			answer: "I am"
		},
		{
			question: '"Mucho gusto" translates to',
			options: ["See you later", "Nice to meet you", "Thank you", "Excuse me"],
			answer: "Nice to meet you"
		},
		{
			question: '"Encantado/a" means',
			options: ["Goodbye", "Nice to meet you", "Thank you", "Sorry"],
			answer: "Nice to meet you"
		},
		{
			question: '"Es un placer" translates to',
			options: ["It's a pleasure", "It's nice", "It's good", "It's great"],
			answer: "It's pleasure"
		},
		{
			question: '"Lo siento" means',
			options: ["I regret", "Sorry", "I apologize", "Pardon"],
			answer: "Sorry (in general)"
		},
		{
			question: '"Lo lamento" translates to',
			options: ["I'm sorry", "I apologize", "Sorry", "I regret"],
			answer: "Sorry (out of regret)"
		},
		{
			question: '"Por favor" means',
			options: ["Thank you", "You're welcome", "Please", "Excuse me"],
			answer: "Please"
		},
		{
			question: '"Gracias" translates to',
			options: ["Please", "Sorry", "Hello", "Thanks"],
			answer: "Thanks"
		},
		{
			question: '"Muchas gracias" means',
			options: ["Thanks a lot", "Thank you", "Thank you so much", "Thanks"],
			answer: "Thank you so much"
		},
		{
			question: '"Muchísimas gracias" translates to',
			options: ["Thanks a lot", "Thank you", "Thank you so much", "Thanks very much"],
			answer: "Thank you very much"
		},
		{
			question: '"De nada" means',
			options: ["It's nothing", "You're welcome", "Don't mention it", "No problem"],
			answer: "Don't mention (in reply to thanks)"
		},
		{
			question: '"Hasta la vista" translates to',
			options: ["See you soon", "See you", "See you later", "Take care"],
			answer: "See you"
		},
		{
			question: '"Hasta pronto" means',
			options: ["See you", "See you later", "See you soon", "Take care"],
			answer: "See you soon"
		},
		{
			question: '"Hasta luego" translates to',
			options: ["See you soon", "Goodbye", "See you later", "Take care"],
			answer: "See you later"
		},
		{
			question: '"Adiós/Chao" means',
			options: ["Hello", "Good morning", "Bye", "See you"],
			answer: "Bye"
		},
		{
			question: '"¡Cuídate!" is an informal way of saying',
			options: ["Hello", "Goodbye", "Take care", "Sorry"],
			answer: "Take care (informal)"
		},
		{
			question: '"¡Cuídese!" translates to',
			options: ["Hello", "Goodbye", "Take care (informal)", "Take care (formal)"],
			answer: "Take care (formal)"
		}
	],
	week6: [
		{
		  "question": "What is the Spanish term for a male lawyer?",
		  "options": [
			"El abogado",
			"La abogada",
			"El actor",
			"La actriz"
		  ],
		  "answer": "El abogado"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the Spanish term for a female lawyer?",
		  "options": [
			"El abogado",
			"La abogada",
			"El agente de viaje",
			"La azafata"
		  ],
		  "answer": "La abogada"
		},
		{
		  "question": "Who is a 'el actor' in Spanish?",
		  "options": [
			"Actor",
			"Singer",
			"Chef",
			"Doctor"
		  ],
		  "answer": "Actor"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the Spanish term for a female travel agent?",
		  "options": [
			"El/La agente de viaje",
			"El/La albañil",
			"El/La azafata",
			"La agente de viaje"
		  ],
		  "answer": "La agente de viaje"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the Spanish term for a male builder?",
		  "options": [
			"El albañil",
			"La albañil",
			"El arquitecto",
			"El cocinero"
		  ],
		  "answer": "El albañil"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the Spanish term for a female architect?",
		  "options": [
			"El arquitecto",
			"La arquitecta",
			"El diseñador",
			"La directora"
		  ],
		  "answer": "La arquitecta"
		},
		{
		  "question": "Who is an 'el anfitrión' in Spanish?",
		  "options": [
			"Host",
			"Assistant",
			"Actor",
			"Author"
		  ],
		  "answer": "Host"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the Spanish term for a female attorney?",
		  "options": [
			"El apoderado",
			"La apoderada",
			"El abogado",
			"La abogada"
		  ],
		  "answer": "La apoderada"
		},
		{
		  "question": "Who is a 'el arquitecto' in Spanish?",
		  "options": [
			"Architect",
			"Cook",
			"Teacher",
			"Photographer"
		  ],
		  "answer": "Architect"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the Spanish term for a female assistant?",
		  "options": [
			"El/La asistente",
			"El/La ama de casa",
			"El autor",
			"La directora"
		  ],
		  "answer": "La asistente"
		},
		{
		  "question": "Who is an 'el ama de casa' in Spanish?",
		  "options": [
			"Home maker",
			"Teacher",
			"Executive",
			"Businessman"
		  ],
		  "answer": "Home maker"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the Spanish term for a female author?",
		  "options": [
			"El autor",
			"La autora",
			"El cocinero",
			"La médica"
		  ],
		  "answer": "La autora"
		},
		{
		  "question": "Who is an 'el azafata' in Spanish?",
		  "options": [
			"Flight attendant",
			"Singer",
			"Chef",
			"Photographer"
		  ],
		  "answer": "Flight attendant"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the Spanish term for a male fireman?",
		  "options": [
			"El bombero",
			"La bombera",
			"El escritor",
			"La escritora"
		  ],
		  "answer": "El bombero"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the Spanish term for a female singer?",
		  "options": [
			"El/La cantante",
			"El/La periodista",
			"El/La fotógrafo",
			"La directora"
		  ],
		  "answer": "La cantante"
		},
		{
		  "question": "Who is an 'el cantautor' in Spanish?",
		  "options": [
			"Lyricist cum singer",
			"Actor",
			"Driver",
			"Chef"
		  ],
		  "answer": "Lyricist cum singer"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the Spanish term for a male waiter?",
		  "options": [
			"El camarero",
			"La camarera",
			"El director",
			"La periodista"
		  ],
		  "answer": "El camarero"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the Spanish term for a female postman?",
		  "options": [
			"La cartera",
			"El cartero",
			"El carpintero",
			"El bombero"
		  ],
		  "answer": "La cartera"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the Spanish term for a male carpenter?",
		  "options": [
			"El carpintero",
			"La carpintera",
			"El vendedor",
			"El maestro"
		  ],
		  "answer": "El carpintero"
		},
		{
		  "question": "Who is an 'el casero' in Spanish?",
		  "options": [
			"Landlord",
			"Businessman",
			"Teacher",
			"Photographer"
		  ],
		  "answer": "Landlord"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the Spanish term for a female scientist?",
		  "options": [
			"El científico",
			"La científica",
			"El/La estilista",
			"El médico"
		  ],
		  "answer": "La científica"
		},
		{
		  "question": "Who is an 'el cineaste' in Spanish?",
		  "options": [
			"Filmmaker",
			"Cook",
			"Doctor",
			"Electrician"
		  ],
		  "answer": "Filmmaker"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the Spanish term for a female surgeon?",
		  "options": [
			"El cirujano",
			"La cirujana",
			"El director",
			"La directora"
		  ],
		  "answer": "La cirujana"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the Spanish term for a male cook?",
			"options": [
			  "El cocinero",
			  "La cocinera",
			  "El conductor",
			  "El doctor"
			],
			"answer": "El cocinero"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "What is the Spanish term for a female driver?",
			"options": [
			  "El conductor",
			  "La conductora",
			  "La directora",
			  "La secretaria"
			],
			"answer": "La conductora"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "Who is an 'el consejero' in Spanish?",
			"options": [
			  "Adviser; Counselor",
			  "Businessman",
			  "Judge",
			  "Dentist"
			],
			"answer": "Adviser; Counselor"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "What is the Spanish term for a female accountant?",
			"options": [
			  "El contador",
			  "La contadora",
			  "La asistente",
			  "El bibliotecario"
			],
			"answer": "La contadora"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "What is the Spanish term for a male servant?",
			"options": [
			  "El criado",
			  "La criada",
			  "El azafata",
			  "El científico"
			],
			"answer": "El criado"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "Who is an 'el dentista' in Spanish?",
			"options": [
			  "Dentist",
			  "Driver",
			  "Fireman",
			  "Author"
			],
			"answer": "Dentist"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "What is the Spanish term for a male director?",
			"options": [
			  "El director",
			  "La directora",
			  "El diseñador",
			  "El estilista"
			],
			"answer": "El director"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "What is the Spanish term for a female designer?",
			"options": [
			  "El diseñador",
			  "La diseñadora",
			  "El médico",
			  "La médica"
			],
			"answer": "La diseñadora"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "Who is an 'el doctor' in Spanish?",
			"options": [
			  "Doctor",
			  "Electrician",
			  "Engineer",
			  "Artist"
			],
			"answer": "Doctor"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "What is the Spanish term for a male executive?",
			"options": [
			  "El ejecutivo",
			  "La ejecutiva",
			  "El empresario",
			  "El enfermero"
			],
			"answer": "El ejecutivo"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "What is the Spanish term for a female electrician?",
			"options": [
			  "El/La electricista",
			  "El/La estilista",
			  "El/La cineaste",
			  "La enfermera"
			],
			"answer": "El/La electricista"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "Who is an 'el empresario' in Spanish?",
			"options": [
			  "Entrepreneur",
			  "Writer",
			  "Driver",
			  "Filmmaker"
			],
			"answer": "Entrepreneur"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "What is the Spanish term for a male nurse?",
			"options": [
			  "El enfermero",
			  "La enfermera",
			  "El estilista",
			  "El fontanero"
			],
			"answer": "El enfermero"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "What is the Spanish term for a female writer?",
			"options": [
			  "El escritor",
			  "La escritora",
			  "El/La estilista",
			  "El piloto"
			],
			"answer": "La escritora"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "Who is an 'el estilista' in Spanish?",
			"options": [
			  "Stylist",
			  "Tailor",
			  "Plumber",
			  "Mechanic"
			],
			"answer": "Stylist"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "What is the Spanish term for a male photographer?",
			"options": [
			  "El fotógrafo",
			  "La fotógrafa",
			  "El bibliotecario",
			  "El maestro"
			],
			"answer": "El fotógrafo"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "What is the Spanish term for a female librarian?",
			"options": [
			  "El bibliotecario",
			  "La bibliotecaria",
			  "El/La periodista",
			  "La maestra"
			],
			"answer": "La bibliotecaria"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "Who is an 'el campesino' in Spanish?",
			"options": [
			  "Peasant; Farmer",
			  "Landlord",
			  "Painter",
			  "Fireman"
			],
			"answer": "Peasant; Farmer"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "What is the Spanish term for a female manager?",
			"options": [
			  "El gerente",
			  "La gerente",
			  "El/La fabricante",
			  "El/La cineaste"
			],
			"answer": "La gerente"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "Who is an 'el guionista' in Spanish?",
			"options": [
			  "Screenwriter",
			  "Singer",
			  "Poet",
			  "Barber"
			],
			"answer": "Screenwriter"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "What is the Spanish term for a female judge?",
			"options": [
			  "El juez",
			  "La jueza",
			  "El lector",
			  "La lectora"
			],
			"answer": "La jueza"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "Who is an 'el lector' in Spanish?",
			"options": [
			  "Reader",
			  "Designer",
			  "Lyricist",
			  "Driver"
			],
			"answer": "Reader"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "What is the Spanish term for a male mechanic?",
			"options": [
			  "El mecánico",
			  "La mecánica",
			  "El maestro",
			  "El modelo"
			],
			"answer": "El mecánico"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "Who is an 'el piloto' in Spanish?",
			"options": [
			  "Pilot",
			  "Soldier",
			  "Driver",
			  "Tailor"
			],
			"answer": "Pilot"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "What is the Spanish term for a male politician?",
			"options": [
			  "El político",
			  "La política",
			  "El director",
			  "El estilista"
			],
			"answer": "El político"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "Who is an 'el profesor' in Spanish?",
			"options": [
			  "Professor",
			  "Dentist",
			  "Cook",
			  "Scientist"
			],
			"answer": "Professor"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "What is the Spanish term for a male representative?",
			"options": [
			  "El representante",
			  "La representante",
			  "El recepcionista",
			  "El revisor"
			],
			"answer": "El representante"
		  },
		  {
			"question": "Who is an 'el secretario' in Spanish?",
			"options": [
			  "Secretary",
			  "Receptionist",
			  "Singer",
			  "Entrepreneur"
			],
			"answer": "Secretary"
		  }
	  ],
	  week7: [
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Aumentar' mean in English?",
		  "options": [
			"To increase",
			"To finish",
			"To feed",
			"To walk"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To increase"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Acabar' mean?",
		  "options": [
			"To finish",
			"To hunt",
			"To hold",
			"To change"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To finish"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of 'Alimentar'?",
		  "options": [
			"To feed",
			"To cut",
			"To cook",
			"To climb"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To feed"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Bailar' translate to?",
		  "options": [
			"To dance",
			"To cook",
			"To walk",
			"To talk"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To dance"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the English meaning of 'Cambiar'?",
		  "options": [
			"To change",
			"To leave",
			"To imagine",
			"To push"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To change"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Cortar' mean in English?",
		  "options": [
			"To cut",
			"To cook",
			"To complete",
			"To save"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To cut"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Dejar' mean?",
		  "options": [
			"To leave",
			"To help",
			"To enter",
			"To gift"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To leave"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Entrar' mean?",
		  "options": [
			"To enter",
			"To hope",
			"To fill",
			"To touch"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To enter"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of 'Escuchar'?",
		  "options": [
			"To listen",
			"To talk",
			"To dance",
			"To plant"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To listen"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Firmar' mean in English?",
		  "options": [
			"To sign",
			"To win",
			"To cut",
			"To consider"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To sign"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Hablar' mean?",
		  "options": [
			"To talk/speak",
			"To embrace",
			"To teach",
			"To imagine"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To talk/speak"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the English meaning of 'Llenar'?",
		  "options": [
			"To fill",
			"To fit",
			"To climb",
			"To depend"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To fill"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Necesitar' mean?",
		  "options": [
			"To need",
			"To carry",
			"To repair",
			"To believe"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To need"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of 'Plantar'?",
		  "options": [
			"To plant",
			"To hunt",
			"To hope",
			"To scale"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To plant"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Cocinar' translate to?",
		  "options": [
			"To cook",
			"To consider",
			"To look",
			"To learn"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To cook"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Comprar' mean?",
		  "options": [
			"To buy",
			"To change",
			"To open",
			"To search"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To buy"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of 'Esperar'?",
		  "options": [
			"To hope/wait",
			"To walk",
			"To listen",
			"To sign"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To hope/wait"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Practicar' mean?",
		  "options": [
			"To practice",
			"To teach",
			"To gift",
			"To polish"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To practice"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Usar' translate to?",
		  "options": [
			"To use",
			"To unite",
			"To imagine",
			"To lift"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To use"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Leer' mean?",
		  "options": [
			"To read",
			"To write",
			"To climb",
			"To decide"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To read"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of 'Escribir'?",
		  "options": [
			"To write",
			"To cover",
			"To save",
			"To smoke"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To write"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Abrir' mean in English?",
		  "options": [
			"To open",
			"To climb",
			"To teach",
			"To wait"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To open"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of 'Recibir'?",
		  "options": [
			"To receive",
			"To recharge",
			"To split",
			"To plant"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To receive"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Trabajar' mean?",
		  "options": [
			"To work",
			"To sell",
			"To discuss",
			"To eat"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To work"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the English meaning of 'Vender'?",
		  "options": [
			"To sell",
			"To break",
			"To download",
			"To decide"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To sell"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Viajar' translate to?",
		  "options": [
			"To travel",
			"To search",
			"To fit",
			"To embrace"
		  ],
		  "answer": "To travel"
		}
	  ],	  
	  week8: [
		{
		  "question": "What is 'Domingo' in English?",
		  "options": ["Sunday", "Monday", "Saturday", "Wednesday"],
		  "answer": "Sunday"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'Viernes' in English?",
		  "options": ["Thursday", "Friday", "Tuesday", "Saturday"],
		  "answer": "Friday"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Son las ocho de la noche' mean?",
		  "options": [
			"Eight o'clock in the night",
			"Eight o'clock in the morning",
			"Eight o'clock at noon",
			"Eight o'clock in the evening"
		  ],
		  "answer": "Eight o'clock in the night"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of 'Es la una y cuarenta'?",
		  "options": ["One forty", "Quarter to two", "Two ten", "One thirty"],
		  "answer": "One forty"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'El año bisiesto' mean?",
		  "options": ["Leap year", "Next year", "Past year", "This year"],
		  "answer": "Leap year"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'El próximo mes' in English?",
		  "options": ["Next month", "Last month", "This month", "Every month"],
		  "answer": "Next month"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Hoy en día' mean?",
		  "options": ["Nowadays", "Tomorrow", "Today", "Yesterday"],
		  "answer": "Nowadays"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'La medianoche' in English?",
		  "options": ["Midnight", "Morning", "Noon", "Evening"],
		  "answer": "Midnight"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'La semana pasada' mean?",
		  "options": ["Last week", "This week", "Next week", "Every week"],
		  "answer": "Last week"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the English translation of 'El mediodía'?",
		  "options": ["Noon", "Night", "Evening", "Morning"],
		  "answer": "Noon"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Todos los días' mean?",
		  "options": ["Every day", "Today", "Daily", "Later"],
		  "answer": "Every day"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'El antes ayer' in English?",
		  "options": [
			"The day before yesterday",
			"Yesterday",
			"Today",
			"Tomorrow"
		  ],
		  "answer": "The day before yesterday"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'Anoche' in English?",
		  "options": ["Last night", "Tonight", "Later", "Tomorrow night"],
		  "answer": "Last night"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'El próximo fin de semana' mean?",
		  "options": [
			"Next weekend",
			"Last weekend",
			"This weekend",
			"Weekend"
		  ],
		  "answer": "Next weekend"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Son las dos y media' mean?",
		  "options": ["Half past two", "Two o'clock", "Quarter past two", "Two forty"],
		  "answer": "Half past two"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Milisegundos' mean?",
		  "options": ["Milliseconds", "Seconds", "Minutes", "Hours"],
		  "answer": "Milliseconds"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Diariamente' mean?",
		  "options": ["Daily", "Yesterday", "Today", "Tomorrow"],
		  "answer": "Daily"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'El pasado mañana' in English?",
		  "options": [
			"The day after tomorrow",
			"Tomorrow",
			"Yesterday",
			"The day before yesterday"
		  ],
		  "answer": "The day after tomorrow"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Esta noche' mean?",
		  "options": ["Tonight", "Last night", "Tomorrow night", "Later"],
		  "answer": "Tonight"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'El año' in English?",
		  "options": ["Year", "Month", "Century", "Week"],
		  "answer": "Year"
		}
	  ],	  
	  week9: [
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Alto/a' mean?",
		  "options": ["Tall", "Short", "Thin", "Big"],
		  "answer": "Tall"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of 'Gordo/a'?",
		  "options": ["Fat", "Thin", "Friendly", "Happy"],
		  "answer": "Fat"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Bonito/a' mean?",
		  "options": ["Pretty", "Ugly", "Small", "Ancient"],
		  "answer": "Pretty"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'Pequeño/a' in English?",
		  "options": ["Small", "Big", "Short", "Wide"],
		  "answer": "Small"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Bueno/a' mean?",
		  "options": ["Good", "Bad", "Better", "Modern"],
		  "answer": "Good"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of 'Frío/a'?",
		  "options": ["Cold", "Hot", "Smooth", "Warm"],
		  "answer": "Cold"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Moderno/a' mean?",
		  "options": ["Modern", "Ancient", "New", "Friendly"],
		  "answer": "Modern"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'Bajo/a' in English?",
		  "options": ["Short", "Tall", "Thin", "Wide"],
		  "answer": "Short"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Inteligente' mean?",
		  "options": ["Intelligent", "Foolish", "Energetic", "Lazy"],
		  "answer": "Intelligent"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'Feo/a' in English?",
		  "options": ["Ugly", "Pretty", "Pleasant", "Friendly"],
		  "answer": "Ugly"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Grande' mean?",
		  "options": ["Big", "Small", "Tall", "Wide"],
		  "answer": "Big"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'Malo/a' in English?",
		  "options": ["Bad", "Good", "Better", "Difficult"],
		  "answer": "Bad"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Caliente' mean?",
		  "options": ["Hot", "Cold", "Smooth", "Soft"],
		  "answer": "Hot"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of 'Nuevo/a'?",
		  "options": ["New", "Old", "Ancient", "Modern"],
		  "answer": "New"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Alegre' mean?",
		  "options": ["Happy", "Sad", "Unhappy", "Hostile"],
		  "answer": "Happy"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'Feliz' in English?",
		  "options": ["Happy", "Sad", "Unhappy", "Interesting"],
		  "answer": "Happy"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Mejor' mean?",
		  "options": ["Better; Best", "Good", "Big", "Pleasant"],
		  "answer": "Better; Best"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'Difícil' in English?",
		  "options": ["Difficult", "Easy", "Costly", "Cheap"],
		  "answer": "Difficult"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Caro/a' mean?",
		  "options": ["Costly", "Cheap", "Easy", "Hard"],
		  "answer": "Costly"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of 'Triste'?",
		  "options": ["Sad", "Happy", "Unhappy", "Pleasant"],
		  "answer": "Sad"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Interesante' mean?",
		  "options": ["Interesting", "Boring", "Amusing", "Hostile"],
		  "answer": "Interesting"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'Fácil' in English?",
		  "options": ["Easy", "Difficult", "Cheap", "Costly"],
		  "answer": "Easy"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Barato/a' mean?",
		  "options": ["Cheap", "Costly", "Difficult", "Long"],
		  "answer": "Cheap"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'Perezoso/a' in English?",
		  "options": ["Lazy", "Energetic", "Gentle", "Friendly"],
		  "answer": "Lazy"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Desagradable' mean?",
		  "options": ["Unpleasant", "Pleasant", "Hostile", "Happy"],
		  "answer": "Unpleasant"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'Rico/a' in English?",
		  "options": ["Rich", "Poor", "Wide", "Big"],
		  "answer": "Rich"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Viejo/a' mean?",
		  "options": ["Old", "New", "Ancient", "Modern"],
		  "answer": "Old"
		}
	  ],	  
	  week10: [
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Rosa' mean?",
		  "options": ["Pink", "Blue", "Red", "Purple"],
		  "answer": "Pink"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of 'Verde'?",
		  "options": ["Green", "Grey", "Orange", "Blue"],
		  "answer": "Green"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Negro/a' mean?",
		  "options": ["Black", "White", "Brown", "Grey"],
		  "answer": "Black"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'Amarillo/a' in English?",
		  "options": ["Yellow", "Golden", "Orange", "Red"],
		  "answer": "Yellow"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Plateado/a' mean?",
		  "options": ["Silvery", "Golden", "Bright", "Dark"],
		  "answer": "Silvery"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of 'El hogar'?",
		  "options": ["Home", "Roof", "Floor", "Kitchen"],
		  "answer": "Home"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'El techo' mean?",
		  "options": ["Roof", "Ceiling", "Wall", "Floor"],
		  "answer": "Roof"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'La ventana' in English?",
		  "options": ["Window", "Wall", "Shelter", "Room"],
		  "answer": "Window"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'El dormitorio' mean?",
		  "options": ["Bedroom", "Living room", "Study room", "Bathroom"],
		  "answer": "Bedroom"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'El baño' in English?",
		  "options": ["Bathroom", "Store room", "Terrace", "Dining room"],
		  "answer": "Bathroom"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'La cocina' mean?",
		  "options": ["Kitchen", "Bathroom", "Garden", "Bedroom"],
		  "answer": "Kitchen"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of 'El jardín'?",
		  "options": ["Garden", "Terrace", "Lawn", "Vegetable garden"],
		  "answer": "Garden"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'El balcón' mean?",
		  "options": ["Balcony", "Portico", "Veranda", "Staircase"],
		  "answer": "Balcony"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'El suelo' in English?",
		  "options": ["Floor", "Wall", "Roof", "Ceiling"],
		  "answer": "Floor"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Cero' mean?",
		  "options": ["Zero", "One", "Half", "Quarter"],
		  "answer": "Zero"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of 'Primero/a'?",
		  "options": ["First", "Second", "Third", "Fourth"],
		  "answer": "First"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Tercero/a' mean?",
		  "options": ["Third", "First", "Second", "Fourth"],
		  "answer": "Third"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'Séptimo/a' in English?",
		  "options": ["Seventh", "Sixth", "Eighth", "Ninth"],
		  "answer": "Seventh"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Décimo/a' mean?",
		  "options": ["Tenth", "Twentieth", "Eighth", "Ninth"],
		  "answer": "Tenth"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of 'Cuarta parte'?",
		  "options": ["Quarter", "Half", "Three quarters", "Zero"],
		  "answer": "Quarter"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Medio/a' mean?",
		  "options": ["Half", "Quarter", "Full", "Three quarters"],
		  "answer": "Half"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'Vigésimo/a' in English?",
		  "options": ["Twentieth", "Tenth", "Eighth", "Seventh"],
		  "answer": "Twentieth"
		}
	  ],	  
	  week11: [
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Encantado/a' mean?",
		  "options": ["Delighted", "Grateful", "Satisfied", "Excited"],
		  "answer": "Delighted"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of 'Emocionado/a'?",
		  "options": ["Excited", "Relieved", "Proud", "Happy"],
		  "answer": "Excited"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Agradecido/a' mean?",
		  "options": ["Grateful", "Relaxed", "Satisfied", "Comfortable"],
		  "answer": "Grateful"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'Preocupado/a' in English?",
		  "options": ["Worried", "Overwhelmed", "Depressed", "Sad"],
		  "answer": "Worried"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Dolido/a' mean?",
		  "options": ["Hurt", "Angry", "Sad", "Uncomfortable"],
		  "answer": "Hurt"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of 'Ansioso/a'?",
		  "options": ["Anxious", "Nervous", "Jealous", "Frustrated"],
		  "answer": "Anxious"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Furioso/a' mean?",
		  "options": ["Furious", "Angry", "Frustrated", "Proud"],
		  "answer": "Furious"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'Sorprendido/a' in English?",
		  "options": ["Surprised", "Optimistic", "Sensitive", "Comfortable"],
		  "answer": "Surprised"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Cansado/a' mean?",
		  "options": ["Tired", "Busy", "Restless", "Timid"],
		  "answer": "Tired"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of '¿Dónde?'?",
		  "options": ["Where?", "When?", "Who?", "Why?"],
		  "answer": "Where?"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does '¿Quiénes?' mean?",
		  "options": ["Who all?", "Who?", "Whose?", "With whom?"],
		  "answer": "Who all?"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is '¿Cómo?' in English?",
		  "options": ["How?", "Where?", "Why?", "When?"],
		  "answer": "How?"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does '¿Cuántos/as?' mean?",
		  "options": ["How many?", "How much?", "How often?", "How many times?"],
		  "answer": "How many?"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of '¿De quién?'?",
		  "options": ["Whose?", "With whom?", "Who?", "Why?"],
		  "answer": "Whose?"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does '¿Cuántas veces?' mean?",
		  "options": ["How many times?", "How much?", "How often?", "How many?"],
		  "answer": "How many times?"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is '¿Por qué?' in English?",
		  "options": ["Why?", "Who?", "What?", "When?"],
		  "answer": "Why?"
		}
	  ],	  
	  week12: [
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Alguien' mean?",
		  "options": ["Someone", "No one", "Something", "Everyone"],
		  "answer": "Someone"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of 'Nada'?",
		  "options": ["Nothing", "Everything", "Anything", "Few"],
		  "answer": "Nothing"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Demasiado/a(s)' mean?",
		  "options": ["Too much", "A lot", "Enough", "Little"],
		  "answer": "Too much"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the English meaning of 'Siempre'?",
		  "options": ["Always", "Never", "Sometimes", "Rarely"],
		  "answer": "Always"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Mismo/a(s)' mean?",
		  "options": ["Same", "Different", "Other", "Few"],
		  "answer": "Same"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'A través de' in English?",
		  "options": ["Through", "After", "Underneath", "Next to"],
		  "answer": "Through"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Cerca de' mean?",
		  "options": ["Close to", "Far from", "Inside of", "Behind"],
		  "answer": "Close to"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of 'Encima de'?",
		  "options": ["On top of", "Underneath", "Between", "In front of"],
		  "answer": "On top of"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Según' mean?",
		  "options": ["According to", "Despite", "Across", "Along with"],
		  "answer": "According to"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the English meaning of 'Ir'?",
		  "options": ["To go", "To take", "To turn", "To cross"],
		  "answer": "To go"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Subir' mean?",
		  "options": ["To go up", "To get down", "To cross", "To bend"],
		  "answer": "To go up"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'La carretera' in English?",
		  "options": ["Highway", "Square", "Building", "Bridge"],
		  "answer": "Highway"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'El semáforo' mean?",
		  "options": ["Traffic light", "Bridge", "Intersection", "Path"],
		  "answer": "Traffic light"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is 'Recto' in English?",
		  "options": ["Straight", "Left", "Right", "Next to"],
		  "answer": "Straight"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'A la derecha' mean?",
		  "options": ["To/on the right", "To/on the left", "Next to", "In front of"],
		  "answer": "To/on the right"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What is the meaning of 'La plaza'?",
		  "options": ["Square", "Park", "Bridge", "Path"],
		  "answer": "Square"
		},
		{
		  "question": "What does 'Al final de' mean?",
		  "options": ["At the end of", "Next to", "Straight ahead", "Close to"],
		  "answer": "At the end of"
		}
	  ],
	  	  
};
